So let's start by setting loading to true when we start fetching a burger, for that I need a new action
Dolaysyla, ykleme yapmaya balaynca yklemeyi true olarak ayarlayarak balayalm ya da eylemin yazld
type, I'll add it to my action types folder, file excuse me and I'll name it PURCHASE_BURGER_START
klasr dosyasna eklenen yeni bir eylem trne ihtiyacm olduu iin, ltfen bana Che'nin burger bana ismini koyacam.
and that will also be my identifier.
Balayn ve bu da benim tanmlaycm olacak.
Now I'll create an action creator for this,
imdi Altria bunun iin yaratt.
we have one which is named like this
Bunun gibi bir tane var.
but this has our async code and therefore doesn't return an action, so I'll
Fakat bunun async kodumuz var ve bu nedenle bir eylem topra dndrmyor.
actually refactor this
Aslnda Reflektor yapar.
and I'll add a new action creator.
Ve yeni bir Eylem Oluturucu ekleyeceim.
This one I'll name purchaseBurgerStart and the old one I'll rename to just purchaseBurger. Now in purchase
Bu bir isim Bergere'yi satn alyor ve eskisinin hepsi imdi Bergere'yi satn almak iin yeniden adlandryor, imdi
BurgerStart
Burger'in startn alyor.
I don't expect any arguments and all I want to do is I want to return a javascript object where the type is
Yapmak istediim herhangi bir argman hi tccar nesne dndrmek iin bir javascript nesnesi dndrmek iin beklemiyorum
set to actionTypes.PURCHASE_BURGER_START so that I can handle this in redux because this being a
nk tr eylem trlerine ayarlanr Bergere balangc satn alabilirim, bylece bu ii halledebilir ve redkt
async normal action reaches redux which has the reducer.
yapabilirim; nk bu, ezamansz bir normal eylem, redux'e ulayor. azaltr.
Now I renamed this to purchaseBurger so we'll have to take care about this in the index.js file
imdi sadece satn almak iin yeniden adlandrmamz gerekiyor Burger's bu konuda endie iinde
where we export it, we export purchaseBurger now.
olmak zorunda kalacak ya da biz ihracat Bergere'yi imdi ihra ediyoruz.
And now in the order.js file still when I dispatch this, before I sent my post request,
Ve imdi srada Jaspal, gnderdiim istei gndermeden nce bunu daha nce gnderdi.
I want to execute purchaseBurgerStart, this function to dispatch this action right at the start.
Ben bama bu eylemi gndermek iin kovalamaca Bergere'nin bu ilevi balatmas iin idam ettim.
Of course I don't want to execute it like this
Tabii ki bunu byle yrtmek istemiyorum.
I want to execute it wrapped in a dispatch so that the action returned by purchaseBurgerStart is dispatched
Satn alma Burgas'n geri gnderdii eylemin llerle birlikte dkkana gnderilmesi iin
to the store. With that,
bir datlana sarlmak istiyorum.
I need to work on contact data because there, I still dispatch purchaseBurgerStart and I should dispatch
Temas veri zerinde almam gerekiyor, nk satn alma yeniden gndermeye devam ediyorum ve onun
purchaseBurger instead.
yerine Bergere'yi gndermeliyim.
Additionally there is an error in this function here where we get dispatch,
Buna ek olarak, gnderimde bu ite bir hata var.
we of course should return a map of props to functions,
Elbette, sahne haritas ilevlerine dnmeliyiz.
so this part here has to go into the return javascript object, like that.
Dolaysyla burada bu blm, dn javascript nesnesine byle girmelidir.
Now with this we should have our action connected,
imdi bununla, hareketimiz bal olsun.
we can now go back to redux, to the reducer and also handle the case that we just started,
Artk redktre x okumak iin geri dnebilir ve yeni balattmz davay halledebiliriz.
This new action we added a second ago,
Bu yeni hareket ve bir saniye nce ekledik.
so I'll add a new case here,
Bu yzden burada yeni bir vaka ekleyeceim.
the position doesn't matter but I'll add it at the top
Konum nemsiz, ancak en ste ekleyeceim.
and here I'll name this actionTypes.PURCHASE_BURGER_START and there, I want to return a javascript object
Ve adn syle ebeveyn trleri olarak Burger'in balang satn almak ve orada bir javascript nesnesi dnmek
as always, we'll copy the old state
istiyorum her zaman eski devlet kopyalayacak.
to keep my old orders but set loading to true. With that we switch loading,
Eski emirlerimi korumak iin bor ile doru yklemeyi syledi, yklemeyi deitirdik.
we of course now have to make sure that the contact data container, we get loading from our state
Elbette imdi, iletiim verilerinin bulunduu konteynrn eyaletimizden yklenmesini salamalyz.
now, from redux because we're using loading in there to show the spinner and right now, we're referring
imdi Rydex'den, Spener'i gstermek iin oraya ykleme yapyoruz ve u anda devlet yklemesine
to state loading,
atfta bulunuyoruz.
well that is something we don't need anymore in the state of this container,
Bu artk bu kabn halindeyken ihtiyacmz olmayan bir ey.
I'll leave all the controls but i'll actually get rid of the loading property there.
Tm denetimleri brakacam, ancak burada ykleme mlknden kurtulacam.
Instead in mapStateToProps, I'll add the loading prop and map it to state,
Bunun yerine durumu devletle bulutururken Propp yklemesini ekleyip devlete eleyeceim.
and now we can reach out to loading but actually we'll soon combine our reducers so we will have to
douceur'u kontak veri konteynerindeki pervanelere ne zaman atmamz gerektiini grmek iin deitirmeliyiz.
change to see this soon to take the slice of that reducer, of the order reducer here in mapStateToProps
Ve imdi yklemeye ulaabiliriz ama aslnda yaknda reticilerimizi bir araya getireceiz, bu nedenle babann bir
in the contact data container.
dilimini, harita durumundaki dzenli
So for now, I'll leave it like this but we'll soon change it, with the loading prop made available here,
imdilik bunu byle brakacam, ancak yaknda mevcut yl yaplan ykleme probuyla deiecek.
I of course should reach out to this props loading here and not this state loading, let's check if we got
Elbette ki burada bu uygun yklemeye ulamalym ve yalnzca Aberdeen'in devlet ykleme yerlerine sahip olup
any other this.state.loading places,
olmadn kontrol etmekle ykml deil.
no we haven't.
Hayr yapmadk.
The last step is in the same file, in the contact data container to also use mapDispatchToProps and add it
Son olarak ayn dosyadaydm ve ayn zamanda haritaya bunu kullanacak bir kii veri kapsaycs badatrcya eklendi
to the connect function, pass it as a second argument
ve ikinci bir bamsz deiken olarak geti.
so that this really is considered by react-redux.
Yani bu, tepki x tarafndan tepki olarak kabul edilir.
So with that all saved, nothing would work,
Yani eski kasa hibir ey ie yaramazsa.
if we go back, we see that we have a problem here,
Geri dnerseniz, burada bir sorunumuz olduunu greceiz.
we're trying to fetch ingredients and this doesn't work and we also will never be able to
Malzemeleri almaya alyoruz ve bu ie yaramyor ve hepimiz biliyoruz ki
reach our other state here,
burada asla dier eyaletimize eriemeyecek.
the order state because we're not combining any reducers.
Dzen devlettir nk herhangi bir redktr birletirmiyoruz.
So let's fix this error first and let's then start working on combining reducers.
Bu hatay nce dzeltelim ve sonra redktrleri birletirmeye alalm.